Finding Aid for School of Education (University of Michigan) Publications 1880-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Unit Publications
  - Reports
    - Institutional Report to the National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1983 (Box 6)
    - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1964 (Box 6)
    - Organization and Activities of the School of Education, 1951 (Box 6)
    - Report for the Visiting Committee, 1990 (Box 6)
    - A Report on Education 691-2: "The Intellectual and Social History of Education" by Jerome Johnston, 1986 (Box 6)
    - Report on the School of Education, University of Michigan: Conducted by a Panel of Educators Appointed by the Academy for Educational Development, 1969 (Box 6)
    - The Role of Salaries in Applied Fields as an Influence on Salary Practices in the School of Education, University of Michigan, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Salaries of Faculties at the University of Michigan as a Function of the Extent of Graduate-Professional Activity, 1960 (Box 6)
    - Social Foundations of Education Monograph Series
      - The Regents of the University of Michigan and the Legislature of the State, 1920-1950 no. 2, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Standards of Growth in the Detroit Public Schools, 1921 (Box 6)
    - Study of University of Michigan Programs for the Preparation of Professional Educators
      - vol. 1-2 undated, 2 folders (Box 6)
      - vol. 3 undated (Box 7)
    - Technical Education in Michigan Community Colleges: Current Status of Collegiate Programs, and Feasibility of Pre-Technical Curriculums in High Schools, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Transition Plan, January 16 and February 22, 1984 versions (Box 7)
    - University of Michigan Monographs in Education
      - Verbal Influences on Children's Behavior no. 1, 1939 (Box 7)
      - Effects of Instruction in Cooperation on the Attitudes and Conduct of Children, no. 2, 1942 (Box 7)
      - Community Workshops for Teachers in the Michigan Community Health Project, no. 3, 1942 (Box 7)
      - Studies in the Psychology of Reading, no. 4, 1951 (Box 7)
    - University of Michigan Programs for the Preparation of Professional Educators, 1982 An Institutional Report, 1983 (Box 7)
    - University of Michigan School of Education Institutional Overview and Long-Range Plan, 1989 (Box 7)
    - What Some Public Schools Have Done in Adult Education, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Syllabi
    - A Syllabus of Course 1 in Education, by George L. Jackson, 1911 (Box 7)
  - Brochures
    - Making a World of Difference, 2004 (Box 15)
    - Teacher Education, May 2011 (Box 15)
  - Bulletins
    - Facing the Challenges // Making a Difference, Undated (Box 15)
  - Directories
    - Faculty Profiles, Undated (Box 15)
  - Manuals
    - Master of Arts with Certification -- Elementary, Undated (Box 15)
    - Master of Arts with Certification -- Secondary, Undated (Box 15)
  - Newsletters
    - Innovator, 2004-2006 (Box 15)
  - Programs
    - Spring Commencement, 2012 (Box 15)
  - Reports
    - Cultural Audit, October 2001 (Box 15)
    - Economic Education in America: Applying Experiential Learning to Economic Education, 1978 (Box 15)
    - A Primer on Michigan School Finance 3rd Edition, 1994 (Box 15)
- Sub-Unit Publications
  The Sub-Unit Publications series contains annual reports, brochures, bulletins, directories, histories, manuals, newsletters, proceedings, programs, and reports published by sub-units within the School of Education. Sub-Units for which there is significant material include the Bureau of Educational Reference and Research, Center for Sex Equity in Schools, Center for the Study of Higher and Postsecondary Education, the Center for the Study of Higher Education, Department of Physical Education, Metropolitan Detroit Bureau of School Studies, National Center for Research to Improve Postsecondary Teaching and Learning (NCRIPTAL), Program for Educational Opportunity, the Summer Session, and the Women's Commission. Researchers interested in vocational and occupational programs should look for material under "Department of Vocational Education and Practical Arts," "Occupational Education Programs," and the "Vocational Education Department."
  - Bureau of Accreditation and School Improvement Studies (BASIS)
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Reports, 1985/1986-1987/1988 (Box 7)
    - Brochures circa 1987 (Box 7)
    - Newsletters
      - Letter to Schools, vol. 38-43, 1985-1990 [supersedes Letter to Schools of the Bureau of School Services] (Box 7)
    - Proposals
      - Mali Monitoring/Improvement Project: A Proposal to Develop a Five-Year Program to Significantly Improve the Conditions of Malian Education at the Primary and Secondary Level, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Questionnaires
      - Michigan Accreditation Pilot Study: Elementary School Tentative Staff Data Collection Questionnaire (draft), 1986 (Box 7)
    - Reports
      - Computer Assisted Analysis of School Accreditation Reports, circa 1985 (Box 7)
      - Report of Accreditation, 1987 includes reports from schools throughout the state (Box 7)
      - The University of Michigan Accredited Schools, 1975/76-1989 (Box 7)
      - The 1987 Principal's Report, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Accreditation Standards 1986-1992, undated (Box 13)
  - Bureau of Cooperation with Educational Institutions
    - Leaflets
      - Observations, nos.1-50, [1943]-1948 (Box 7)
  - Bureau of Educational Reference and Research
    - Abstracts
      - Abstracts of Dissertations and Theses in Education, 1917-1932 (Box 7)
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1922-1948 (Box 7)
    - Catalogs
      - Standardized Test and Scales, 1923-1928 (Box 7)
    - Manuals
      - Language Aims: Suggestions and Activities for Their Realization, Undated (Box 7)
    - Reports
      - Bulletin
        - no. 31-95 1921-1926, 5 folders (Box 7)
        - no. 98-158 1927-1948, 12 folders (Box 8)
    - Reprints
      - Current Viewpoints in Education: A Series of Articles by Members of the Faculty, Reprinted from the University of Michigan School of Education Bulletin, compiled by Claude Eggertsen and Warren R. Good, 1942 (Box 8)
      - Education B195f Monographs (Box 8)
        - Social Trends and Curriculum Revision, no. 1, 1935 (Box 8)
        - Innovating Practices in the Curriculum, no. 2, 1935 (Box 8)
      - The Evaluation of Instruction, 1939 (Box 8)
      - Problems Related to Reading Ability and Study Habits, 1939 (Box 8)
  - Bureau of School Services
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 13)
      - Annual Reports, 1970-1978, 3 folders (Box 13)
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 8)
    - Brochures
      - Miscellaneous undated (Box 8)
      - Summer Seminar Series 1969-1971 (Box 13)
    - Newsletters
      - Letter to Schools, vol. 13-37, 1961-1984 (Box 8)
        [precedes Letter to Schools of Bureau of Accreditation and School Improvement Studies]
    - Reports
      - The University of Michigan Accredited Schools, 1984/85 (Box 8)
      - Ann Arbor Schools Study, vol. 1, 1974 (Box 13)
      - Michigan Committee North Central Association Self-Study Report, 1979 (Box 13)
      - Planning Norms and Space Allocations for Elementary and Secondary Schools, 1979 (Box 13)
      - Recommendations on School Finance and Educational Opportunity, 1969 (Box 13)
      - Summary Report: 1978-1979 (Box 13)
    - Michigan Interscholastic Forensic Association
      - Brochures 1984, undated (Box 8)
    - Michigan School Testing Service
      - Brochures 1975 (Box 8)
      - Michigan School Testing Conference
        - Programs 1982-1993 (Box 8)
  - Bureau of Tests and Measurements
    - Reports
      - Bulletin, 1920-1921 no. 1-29 (Box 8)
  - Center for Educational Improvement Through Collaboration
    - Anthologies
      - Corridors: Stories from Inner City Detroit--The Dewey Center Community Writing Project, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Footsteps: Looking Back, Moving On--A Publication by Students from Arthur Hill High School, Saginaw High School, Saginaw, Michigan, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Center for Highly Interactive Computing in Education
    - Brochures 2000 (Box 13)
  - Center for the Improvement of Early Reading Achievement (CIERA)
    - Brochures undated (Box 13)
  - Center for Research on Learning and Schooling
    - Annual Report 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  - Center for Sex Equity in Schools
    - Annual Reports
      [filed with Programs for Educational Opportunity, Annual Reports]
      - 1981/82 (Box 8)
    - Manuals
      - Tune in to Your Rights...A Guide for Teenagers About Turning Off Sexual Harassment, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Journals
      - Title IX Line, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Center for the Study of Higher and Postsecondary Education
    - Annual Reports 1985-1988 (Box 8)
    - Brochures 1988, undated (Box 8)
    - Reports
      - The Culture and Climate for Quality: Perceptions of the Work Environment of the University of Michigan's Non-Instructional Staff, 1994 (Box 8)
    - Professional Preparation Project
      - Manuals
        - PLUSS (Professional/Liberal Undergraduate Self-Study, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Reports
        - Executive Summary of the University of Michigan Professional Preparation Study Project Survey, Undated (Box 8)
      - Surveys
        - Emphases, Processes, and Influences in Professional Preparation Programs, Undated (Box 8)
  - Center for the Study of Higher Education
    - Annual Reports
      - 1957-1982 Twenty-Five Years Leadership and Adaptation: 1981- 82 Report to the Dean, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Bibliographies
      - Dissertations Completed Through December, 1981, Undated (Box 8)
      - Publications in Higher Education, Undated (Box 8)
    - Brochures
      - Undated 1976-1981 (Box 8)
      - 2005 (Box 13)
    - Bulletins
      - Program Leading to the Doctor of Philosophy Degree in Higher Education, 1981-1982, 1981 (Box 8)
      - Programs Leading to the Master of Arts Degree in Higher Education, 1981-1982, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Directories
      - Alumni and Faculty Directory, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Faculty and Staff of CSHPE 1995 (Box 13)
    - Flyers 1987 (Box 8)
    - Manuals
      - Student Manual 1981-1982, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Newsletters
      - CSHE Newsline, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Grapevine, 1959-1962 (Box 8)
      - Newsletter, 1962-1973 (Box 8)
    - Proceedings
      - Structure and Emergence: Proceedings of an Institute of Innovations in Undergraduate Education, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Reports
      - Affirmative Action: Its Legal Mandate and Organizational Implications, 1974 (Box 9)
      - Aid to Higher Education: A Continuing Federal Dilemma, 1975 (Box 9)
      - Higher Education in Michigan, 1960 (draft), by M.M. Chambers, 1960 (Box 9)
      - Implementation of Formal Planning: Strategies for the Large University, 1982 (Box 9)
      - Presidential Views of Higher Education's National Institutional Membership Associations, circa 1980 (Box 9)
      - Projecting College and University Enrollments: Analyzing the Past and Focusing the Future, 1974 (Box 9)
      - The Study of Higher Education, 1950-1966, 1966 (Box 9)
      - Voluntary Statewide Coordination in Higher Education (draft) by M.M. Chambers, 1960 (Box 9)
      - The Proprietary School: Assessing its Impact on the Collegiate Sector, 1975 (Box 13)
      - Task Force Report and Recommendations on the Role of Adult Education at the University of Michigan, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Community College Development Program
      - Brochures Undated (Box 9)
    - Reports
      - Debts and Decisions, 2001 (Box 13)
      - Perceptions of the Work Environment at the University of Michigan, 1944 (Box 13)
  - Chair of the Science and Art of Teaching
    - Centennial
      - Program 1978 (Box 9)
  - Child Care Action Center
    - Brochures undated (Box 9)
  - Children's Center
    - Annual Reports
      - School of Education Involvement in the University of Michigan Children's Center, 1981/82 (Box 9)
  - Combined Program in Education and Psychology
    - Annual Report 1982 (Box 9)
    - Brochures circa 1971-1980, undated (Box 9)
    - Newsletters
      - The Word, v. 7, no. 1-2, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Combined Resources for Educative Electronics
    - Brochures 1973 (Box 9)
  - Committee on Educational Research
    - Newsletters
      - Educational Research Newsletter v. 1-3, 1958-1960 (Box 9)
      - Research Newsletter, v. 4-9, 1960-1969, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies in Education
    - Bulletins
      - Advanced Studies in Education, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
  - Communicative Disorders Clinic
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 9)
  - Consortium for Evaluation Research, Training and Service
    - Annual Reports 1980-1983
      - Advanced Studies in Education, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
  - Counseling and Guidance Institute
    - Brochures 1964/65 (Box 9)
  - Counseling and Personnel Services
    [see also the file, ERIC/CAPS]
    - Brochures Undated, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Newsletters
      - CAPS Capsule, 1969-1985 (Box 9)
  - The Curriculum and Instruction Program
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 9)
  - Curriculum Committee
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 9)
  - Curriculum, Teaching and Psychological Studies Program
    - Directories
      - Student Profiles, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Manuals
      - Student Handbook, 1988-1989 (Box 9)
  - Department of Adult and Continuing Education
    - Newsletters
      - ACE Reporter, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Department of Elementary School Principals
    - Brochures 1937 (Box 9)
  - Department of Physical Education
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1980-1982 (Box 9)
    - Brochures Undated (Box 9)
    - Directories
      - Introduction to School of Education Faculty, 1978 (Box 9)
    - Manuals
      - University of Michigan Student Teacher Handbook, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Newsletters
      - Exercise and Fitness, 1981 (Box 9)
      - Physical Education Newsletter, v. 7, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Undergraduate Programs
      - Brochures Undated (Box 9)
  - Department of Vocational Education and Practical Arts
    - Newsletters
      - Industrial Education Bulletin, 1952/1953-1956/1957, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Newsletter, 1954-1964 (Box 9)
  - Division of Public Health
    - Bulletins
      - Courses in Public Health Nursing, 1934 (Box 9)
  - Early Childhood Education Graduate Program
    - Brochures 1968-1985, undated (Box 9)
  - Early Childhood Lecture Series
    - Brochures 1981-1985 (Box 9)
  - Educational Foundations, Policy and Administration Program
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1986/87-1987/88 (Box 9)
    - Brochures 1987 (Box 9)
  - Educational Media Center
    - Brochures undated (Box 9)
    - Manuals
      - Educational Media Center Handbook, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Newsletters
      - Media Messenger, 1971-1975 (Box 9)
  - Educational Psychology Program
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 9)
  - Educational Resources Information Center/ Counseling and Personnel Services (ERIC/CAPS)
    [see also the file, Counseling and Personnel Services]
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 9)
    - Brochures 1970-1984, undated (Box 9)
    - Catalogs 1985 (Box 9)
    - Flyers
      - Highlights: An ERIC/CAPS Fact Sheet, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
      - In Brief: An Information Digest From ERIC/CAPS, 1984 (Box 9)
    - Magazines
      - Impact, circa 1972 (Box 9)
    - Manuals
      - Counseling Youth for Employabilty: Unleashing the Potential by E.L. Herr and T.E. Long, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Newsletters
      - Communique: A News Sheet for School Counselors, undated (Box 9)
  - Educational Studies Program
    - Brochures 2000, undated (Box 13)
    - Directories
      - Faculty Profiles 1991-1992 (Box 13)
    - Manuals
      - Student Handbook 1990/91, 1995/96 (Box 13)
  - Education and Community Development Program
    - Brochures
      - General Requirements for the Master's Degree, 1973/74 (Box 9)
  - Education Change Team
    - Questionnaires undated (Box 9)
  - Education Library
    - Catalogs 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - English and Education Program
    - Brochures 1981-1982 (Box 9)
    - Newsletters
      - E2A2, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
  - ExCEL
    - Reports
      - A Collaborative Effort in Developing a Model Microcomputer-Assisted Learning Environment, undated (Box 13)
  - The Franfurt-Michigan-Sheffield Cross-Cultural Study Program
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Reports, 1981/82 (Box 9)
  - Fresh Air Camp
    - Brochures undated (Box 9)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee
    - Reports
      - Improving Dissertation Quality, 1986, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Health Occupations Teacher Education Project
    - Reports
      - Improving the Quality of Health Occupations Teachers: A Report or the Health Occupations Teacher Education Project, 1972-1975, 1975 (Box 9)
  - High School Research Project (Box 10)
    - Reports
      - Facts and Feelings: High School Students, Teachers, and Administrators give their Opinions, Undated (Box 10)
  - Innovative Tutorial Experience
    - Brochures undated (Box 10)
  - Instructional, Research and Information Services (IRIS)
    [supersedes Instructional Strategy Services--see sub-series]
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1987/88 (Box 10)
    - Flyers 1988-1990 (Box 10)
    - Newsletters
      - Newsnotes and Ephemera, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Instructional Strategy Services [precedes IRIS--see sub-series]
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1980-1987, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Minutes 1979-1983 (Box 10)
    - Newsletters
      - ISS News Notes, v. 1-8, 1980-1988 (Box 10)
  - Joint Hampton-Michigan Program for Training Minority and Women Researchers (Box 14)
    - Reports
      - Final Report Volume 1 1980 (Box 14)
      - Final Report Volume 2 1980 (Box 14)
  - Leadership Development Program
    - Newsletters
      - Newsletter, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Learning Evaluation Clinic
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 10)
  - Metropolitan Detroit Bureau of School Studies
    - Reports
      - Reports
        - 1977-1982, 5 volumes (Box 10)
      - Salary Analysis of Negotiated Teacher Contracts, 1983-1986 (Box 11)
      - Summary and Analysis of Administrative and Supervisory Salaries and Fringe Benefits in Metropolitan Detroit Schools, 1982-1983 (Box 11)
  - Microcomputer Education Center
    - Brochures 1984-1986 (Box 11)
    - Statistics
      - MEC is..., 1985 (Box 11)
  - Michigan Future Problem Solving Program
    - Brochures undated (Box 14)
    - Newsletters
      - FPS More or Less, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Michigan North Secondary Schools
    - Annual Reports 1949-1961 (Box 14)
  - National Center for Research to Improve Postsecondary Teaching and Learning (NCRIPTAL)
    - Brochures Undated, 1988-1990 (Box 11)
    - Flyers undated (Box 11)
    - Newsletters
      - Accent on Improving College Teaching and Learning, 1989 (Box 11)
      - Update, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Reports
      - Application for Continuation Award, 1988 (Box 11)
      - The Electronic Classroom in Higher Education: A Case for Change, 1989 (Box 11)
      - Organizational Context for Teaching and Learning, 1987 (Box 11)
      - Planning Introductory College Courses: Influences on Faculty, 1989 (Box 11)
      - Psychological Models of the Impact of College on Students, 1986 (Box 11)
      - Quarterly Reports, 1987-1989, 3 folders (Box 11)
    - EDUCOM
      - Newsletters
        - EDUCOM, 1966 (Box 11)
      - Reports
        - Higher Education Software Awards, 1987 (Box 11)
        - Catalog of Winners from the 1987- 90 EDUCOM/NCRIPTAL Higher Education Software Awards Competition, 1990 (Box 11)
  - National Study of Gender Grouping in Independent Secondary Schools
    - Brochures circa 1986 (Box 11)
  - Network on Educational Unrest
    - Brochures undated (Box 11)
  - National Center for Research to Improve Postsecondary Teaching and Learning (NCRIPTAL)
    - Manuals
      - Course Planning Exploration for Program Self-Study User's Manual, 1991 (Box 14)
      - Preparing Course Syllabi for Improved Communication, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Occupational Education Programs
    - Brochures undated (Box 11)
    - Newsletters
      - LDP Newsletter, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Reports
      - The Development and Implementation of Pre-Science and In-Service Occupational Teacher Education Programs Designed to Meet Certification and Baccalaureate Degree Requirements (Report no. 2), 1973 (Box 11)
      - Manpower Leadership Program, 1977-1978, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Office of Academic Services
    - Bulletins
      - Announcement of Courses, 1986 (Box 11)
      - Course Descriptions, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
    - Brochures
      - Graduate Programs in Educational Foundations, Policy and Administration, 1987 (Box 11)
    - Manuals
      - Annual Recruitment and Placement Handbook, 1985/86 (Box 11)
      - Elementary Teacher Certification Manual, 1984-1986 (Box 11)
      - Secondary Teacher Certification Manual, 1984-1986 (Box 11)
  - Office of Community Education Research
    - Abstracts
      - Abstracts: Community Education Research, circa 1975 (Box 11)
    - Bibliographies
      - Community Education Dissertations--1965-1977, 1977 (Box 11)
      - Dissertations Related to Community Education, 1973-1976, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Office of Institutional Research
    - Reports
      - The School of Education 50-Year Report 1972 (Box 11)
  - Office of Instructional Technology
    - Invitations 1989 (Box 11)
  - Office of Minority Affairs
    - Newsletters
      - The Spectrum, 1995-1996 (Box 14)
  - Offices of Research Service
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 11)
  - Office of Student Services
    - Brochures undated (Box 11)
  - The Outdoor Science Resource Center
    - Brochures undated (Box 11)
  - Preservice Technology Training Task Force
    - Reports
      - Technology Training for Michigan's Preservice Teachers, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Professional Development
    - Brochures 1982-1983, undated (Box 11)
    - Newsletters
      - Professional Development Update, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Community College Consortium (Summer Institute)
      - Programs 1987-1989 (Box 11)
  - Professional Preparation Network
    - Reports
      - Strengthening the Ties that Bind: Integrating Undergraduate Liberal and Professional Study, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Program in Curriculum, Teaching, and Psychological Studies
    - Brochures circa 1987 (Box 11)
  - The Program in Educational Administration and Supervision
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 11)
  - Program in Educational Psychology
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 11)
    - Brochures undated (Box 11)
    - Manuals
      - Student Handbook, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Program in Adult and Continuing Education
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 11)
  - Program in Higher and Adult Continuing Education
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1986/87 (Box 11)
    - Brochures circa 1980-1989 (Box 11)
    - Bulletins 1986-1989 (Box 11)
    - Directories
      - Alumni and Faculty Directory 1987 (Box 11)
    - Invitations 1991 (Box 11)
    - Newsletters
      - Pursuit, 1986-1994 (Box 11)
    - Professional Development
      - Brochures undated (Box 11)
      - Community College Consortium
        - Programs 1987 (Box 11)
  - Program in Scholarly Research for Urban/Minority High School Students
    - Booklet 1983 (Box 14)
  - Program in Social Foundations of Education
    - Newsletters
      - Notes and Abstracts in American and International Education, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Program in Special Education
    - Programs 1971 (Box 11)
    - Proceedings
      - Proceedings of the University of Michigan Institute: The Impact and Implications of State and Federal Legislation Affecting Handicapped Individuals, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Program of Speech and Hearing Sciences (Box 12)
    - Annual Reports
      - Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 12)
  - Programs for Educational Opportunity
    - Annual Reports